<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Emulation - Tag - Everyone, meet fel1x</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/emulation/</link>
        <description>Emulation - Tag - Everyone, meet fel1x</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>xuanphuc.a1gv@gmail.com (Felix Hoang)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>xuanphuc.a1gv@gmail.com (Felix Hoang)</webMaster><copyright>2025 Felix</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/emulation/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Run Nintendo Switch Games on iPhone at 60FPS – Free, No Jailbreak Needed</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/emulation-switch-ipad/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Felix Hoang</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/emulation-switch-ipad/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>If you thought the biggest gaming news was the upcoming Switch 2, think again. The emulation community has made a breakthrough: you can now run Nintendo Switch games on your iPhone or iPad at buttery-smooth 60FPS—all offline, with no jailbreak, no shady VPNs, and zero sketchiness.</p>
<data id="id-1" data-raw></data>
<hr>
<h2 id="the-jit-struggle">The JIT Struggle</h2>
<p>Just-In-Time (JIT) compilation is a method used by emulators to dramatically improve performance by converting code into machine instructions while the program is running. Normally, an emulator has to interpret every single instruction one-by-one, which is slow. JIT speeds things up by compiling larger chunks of code in real time, allowing games to run closer to native speeds.
However, Apple has strict security policies that prevent unauthorized JIT execution on iOS devices. There are some workarounds like JITStreamer or SideJITServer but they all require an internet connection. StikJIT and StosVPN now bypass this restriction by enabling JIT locally, without external servers, making offline Nintendo Switch emulation possible on iPhones.
Here&rsquo;s the difference between no JIT vs JIT-enabled when running emulator on iOS.</p>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
