<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Productivity - Tag - Everyone, meet fel1x</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/productivity/</link>
        <description>Productivity - Tag - Everyone, meet fel1x</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>xuanphuc.a1gv@gmail.com (Felix Hoang)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>xuanphuc.a1gv@gmail.com (Felix Hoang)</webMaster><copyright>2025 Felix</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 &#43;0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/productivity/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Organizing My Digital Life - A Nerdy Journey Across Drives, File Management</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/productitvity-file-management/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Felix Hoang</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/productitvity-file-management/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>We all love the idea of being super organized, right? We make these grand plans, give it our all for a few weeks or months, and then, bam! We&rsquo;re back to the good old &ldquo;throw it in the downloads folder with everything else&rdquo; routine. It happens to the best of us, and I&rsquo;m guilty too. But hey, even though I&rsquo;ve still got loads of room for improvement, I can proudly say I&rsquo;ve gotten way faster at finding my files.</p>]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Organizing My Digital Life - How My Workspace Evolved from Chaos to Hackintosh</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/productivity-workspace/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 00:00:00 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Felix Hoang</author>
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/productivity-workspace/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><em>This is the first blog in a series on how I organize my work process, both physically and online. This includes my workspace, file management, and planning.</em></p>
<p>Today, I would like to introduce you to the journey of optimizing my workspace environment, or in simpler terms, my desk setup. In fact, I am not someone who strictly adheres to principles in life. However, I really enjoy working in a disciplined environment and always strive to optimize it for effective studying and working. To achieve the setup I have today, I had to tear down and rebuild this workstation more than 10 times. Finally, I am truly satisfied with it. It not only satisfies me aesthetically but also makes me eager to work as soon as I step into this room (well, not quite true because nowadays most of the time I feel most productive when working from a coffee shop&hellip;).</p>]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
